{
    "id": "3c738dfa34874e6cbde3ae77557ae6f1",
    "title": "Phrasal verbs with stand",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "55862942fee444858cb0bd790b21ef5b",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She was so tired that she couldnâ€™t even stand ...................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her parents are very conservative and stand ................................................ traditional family values.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "for",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Now that John has fallen ill we should find someone else to stand ................................. for him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "in",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He wants to stand ........................................ Parliament at the next election.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "for",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Good friends will stand ........................................ you during both good and bad times.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "with",
                        "by"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "A woman must stand ................................... her man.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "with",
                        "by"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Marc was not the best candidate so it stands ................................... no reason that he got the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "to",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The Apple iPad had many features that made it stand ......................................... from other tablet computers on the market.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "off",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The chairman is standing ...................................... from his position because of ill-health.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The bold girl stood .......................................... the rowdy who tried to misbehave with her and slapped him right across his face.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "up",
                        "up to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}